<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="12"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[A beautiful










                                                BIRD









                                          Created by: Sarra Ben Amara





































                                               English Board Creation]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Dr. Norton’s occupation was a scholar of biology. He learned


       about all animals on a daily basis. One day he met a sailor from

       a colony overseas. The man told Dr. Norton about a talking bird!]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[The bird fascinated Dr. Norton, so he told his colleagues about it.


       They debated with him: no one thought a bird could talk. He tried

       to persuade them, but they laughed at him.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Nevertheless, Dr. Norton believed the bird was real. His new


    mission was to find it. He wanted factual proof. The next day he

    departed for the colony. The sailor he had met told him to look for

    a man named Jai, who would be able to help him in his search.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[After a month of sailing, Dr. Norton finally reached the colony


       where he met Jai.

       “I can take you to where it lives. It lives by the volcano,” Jai said.]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[They left the next day. A week later, they arrived at the volcano.

        Every day they walked around and looked for the bird, but they

        couldn’t find it. After one month, Dr. Norton could not find the


        bird, and this depressed him.]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[He decided to go home. On the route back, he walked past

          some old ruins. He heard someone say, “Hello.”]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[“Who are you?” he asked. Dr. Norton looked up and saw a bird!


         Dr. Norton put the talking bird into a cage. Then he returned

         home. He had made a significant discovery.]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[]]></page></pages></Search>